# **COLETTE KELLY**

Email: <a href="mailto:colettejkelly@gmail.com">colettejkelly@gmail.com</a>

## **SUMMARY**

Currently enrolled in a front-end and back-end web development boot camp. Learning HTML, CSS, GitHub, Javascript, Angular, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Node, Express and Cloud9. My past experience as a nurse has made me an excellent communicator and listener. Patience, problem-solving and being an effective team member are other qualities that I possess that will also help me to be an excellent web developer.

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

## **Health Screening Nurse**, **Flu Shot Nurse**, Provant Health

11/2015 - Present

- Provide biometric screenings to employees in the workplace including cholesterol/glucose checks, blood pressure, body mass index, body fat percentage and health coaching
- Administer flu shots to participants

RN Refresher Program, SFGH/LHH, San Francisco, CA January 2016 – May 2016

 Provide total care of patients at San Francisco General Hospital and Laguna Honda Hospital under supervision of instructor/staff RNs

Blood Bank Nurse, Stanford Blood Center, Palo Alto, CA

2013 - 2013

Assist in the collection of blood from donors

Postpartum Doula/RN, Independent Employers, SF, CA

2011 - Present

- Provide in-home care for high-risk newborn infants in the postpartum period
- Provide education and support to parents in the postpartum period

Manager, San Francisco, CA

1998 - Present

• Manage and provide administrative support for small independent business

#### Registered Nurse, Charge Nurse, Float Nurse

St. Mary's Medical Center, San Francisco, CA

1991 - 1998

- Provide all aspects of medical, rehabilitative and psychosocial care to patients in all units of acute care facility including: Telemetry/Cardiology – Medical - Surgical -Orthopedics - Infectious Diseases - Oncology - Rehabilitation - Ambulatory Care and Skilled Nursing
- Supervise and direct RNs, LVNs and CNAs
- Train and orient new nurses and provide instruction regarding specific tasks and job techniques

Registered Nurse, Independent Employer, San Francisco, CA

1988 - 1991

- Provide nursing care and support for young quadriplegic stroke patient
- Provide assistance with physical therapy and occupational therapy
- Manage appointments and transport patient to appointments

## **LICENSURE/CERTIFICATION**

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

**MEDA** Front and back-end web development including HTML Aug 2020-Dec 2020 CSS, GitHub, Javascript

City College of San Francisco/JVS RN Refresher Course January - May 2016 Over 456 hours of theoretical practice & clinical experience at City College of San Francisco, San Francisco General Hospital and Laguna Honda Hospital

American Health Education, Inc., Dublin, CA RN Refresher Course 2013 Acute care review, IV skills.

Natural Resources, San Francisco, CA Post-Partum Doula Training 2011 Trained in education and support of parents during the postpartum fourth trimester, including techniques to: assist with newborn care and family adjustment, offer evidence-based information on infant feeding, help with emotional and physical recovery of mother after birth, teach coping skills for new parents and make appropriate referrals when necessary.

Medical Advancement Center, Cypress, CA Nursing Skills Update 2009
Acute care review, IV skills/BLS/AED/ACLS

# Adelaide Hospital, Dublin, Ireland

ADN RN

Completed RN clinical and academic training in acute care facility RN license from Irish Nursing Board

## National Children's Hospital, Dublin, Ireland

**ADN RN** 

Completed Pediatric RN clinical and academic training in acute care facility RN pediatric license from Irish Nursing Board